hello guys to add up to our how to
playlist I will be presenting a payment
option for your sunlife insurance and
that is by using the digital wallet Maya
so let's start first you have to log in
to your Maya account and then check if
you have enough balance for your
insurance payment so I have enough I'll
be paying 3,200 and I have more than
6,000 in my account so I can proceed
with my payment so first you have to
click on bills
after Bills select
insurance and then you will be presented
with the different billers insurance
billers so you just have to scroll down
until you find sunlife of Philippines
Canada and then you will see the payment
form you need to fill out the policy
number followed by the amount and then
the product type if you drop this down
you will see traditional or
V and then the account name and then
click
continue so this is how I pay my sun
life insurance so I'll put the policy
number
first and then I'll be paying
3,200 and the product type this is a
V and I will encode my
name so press continue and then you will
be directed to the confirmation page
double check the details you encoded and
if everything is fine just click pay and
then that's it you are done you may take
a screenshot of this transaction for
your future reference though you will
also receive a text message for this
specific
transaction and just wait for the copy
of your receipt to be sent to your
registered email address so I paid this
on June 22 and I received the email
confirmation and my receipt from sunlife
on June
24th so that's it very easy and very
convenient way to pay your sunlife
insurance aside from Maya you may also
use gcash or your BPI internet banking
we have this videos posted already
please check this videos if you're still
looking for other payment options for
your sunlife insurance okay that's it
thank you very much for watching please
support our Channel please like And
subscribe thank you bye